Every night before bed a father would
stop by his son's room to say goodnight.
It was their tradition,
one he never missed.
His son could never sleep well without it.
Tonight seemed no different.
The room was dimly lit by a small bedside lamp,
but as he stepped inside,
something
felt off.
His son sat upright in bed,
silent,
wearing an impossibly wide grin.
You okay, buddy?
The father asked.
The boy slowly nodded, then he whispered,
Daddy,
can you check for monsters under my bed?
The father smiled and knelt beside the bed.
He lifted the blanket and looked underneath,
and there,
curled up in the darkness,
was his son,
pale,
shaking,
terrified.
The boy looked up at him and whispered, Daddy,
there's someone on my bed.